Jason Chen

ADDRESS: 1/108 Huia Road

Point Chevalier Auckland 1022

MOBILE: 021 165 7705

EMAIL: jason.chen940501@gmail.com

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jian-chen-2018/

GITHUB: https://github.com/CHENJ137

PERSONAL STATEMENT

The most important attribute I have is my enthusiasm to learn and to do a job well. I have genuine interests in Technology and in Arts and with my work experience they have helped make me become grounded in my approach to work and attitude towards a job.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUN 2019 - PRESENT

MYLOTTO HELPDESK SUPPORT (Full-Time for 3 months, currently Part-Time)

LOTTO NEW ZEALAND - AUCKLAND

- Troubleshooting online customer connectivity issues
- Problem solving account queries
- Retail Customer Support

JUL 2018 - SEP 2018

MAINTENANCE OFFICER (Part-Time)

CARE PARK - WELLINGTON

- Attend to and fix ticket machines, pay stations and any other parking related equipment as required
- Complete preventative maintenance tasks of ticket machines, pay stations and any other parking related equipment as per the maintenance schedule
- Assisting operations with tasks as requested

FEB 2017 - APR 2018

CREW TRAINER

McDONALD'S POINT CHEVALIER - AUCKLAND

- Support and train crew members to ensure they are effective and competent in their role
- Update the new crew members' SOCs (a training programme of McDonald's)

MAR 2015 - OCT 2015

INTERNSHIP - WEB DEVELOPMENT

SHANGHAI QINGYU EQUITY INVESTMENT FUND MANAGEMENT CO. LTD

EDUCATION

FEB 2017 - NOV 2017

GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN COMPUTING

UNITEC INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY – NEW ZEALAND

Completed courses include: - Project Planning and Control - Testing/Quality Assurance ICT

- GUI Programming

- Testing/Quality Assurance Management

- Agile & Lean Software Delivery- Business Systems Analysis

Information Systems & AnalysisInformation Systems Management

SEP 2011 - JUN 2015

BACHELOR OF ECONOMICS

HENAN AGRICULTURE UNIVERSITY (HAU) - CHINA

SKILLS AND OTHER EXEPREINCE

KEY TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Experience in a Help Desk environment
- Advanced skills to analyse and resolve support requests from end users
- Profound understanding of LAN and WAN management and maintenance protocols
- Proficiency with MS Office Applications, VMWare, Internet Browsers and VoIP system.
- DB: MySQL, Oracle, redis, Memcached
- Web Server: Apache, Nginx
- OS: Mac OS, Windows, CentOS, Ubuntu
- Agile Development: Scrum, SDLC.

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

- Excellent phone etiquette and customer service skills
- Fluent spoken and written English and Chinese
- Competent in researching and creating written reports
- Strong team spirit engendered among staff in leadership role as crew trainer

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Confident with a thorough sense of responsibility, treating people with respect and sincerity
- Goal-oriented with motivation to learn and apply knowledge in practical contexts

ACHIEVEMENTS

| NOV 2017 | Recognised as Crew of the Month at McDonald's Point Chevalier |
|----------|--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------|
| OCT 2017 | ABCTestProject - A project for test management and bug tracking based on C# language |
| JUN 2017 | ICAgile Certified Professional |
| JUN 2015 | Self-Starter with installing remote monitoring system for private property |
| | Awarded the Excellent Student Scholarship 5 times during undergraduate |

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Drawing Attended annual art festivals held at school
- Sports and Fitness Hiking, Martial Art Karate (Currently as 7th kyu)
- Travelling Working Holiday in New Zealand for one year, cultural exchanges

REFEREES

Victor Hukui **CUSTOMER SERVICES MANAGER** LOTTO NEW ZEALAND 027 801 2431 victor.hukui@lottonz.co.nz

Melissa Waamu **OPERATIONS TEAM LEADER** CARE PARK NEW ZEALAND 021 193 9122 Melissa.W@carepark.co.nz